<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>FlowSync</title>
  <link href="http://localhost:3000" />
  <link href="http://localhost:3000/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <updated>2026-02-26T05:58:03Z</updated>
  <id>http://localhost:3000</id>
  <subtitle>Team collaboration, reimagined</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>FlowSync Launches v2.0: A Complete Redesign</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:3000/blog/flowsync-launches-v2/" />
    <id>http://localhost:3000/blog/flowsync-launches-v2/</id>
    <updated>2026-02-14T15:00:00Z</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re thrilled to announce &lt;strong&gt;FlowSync v2.0&lt;/strong&gt;, the biggest update since our launch. After months of user research, prototyping, and engineering work, we&apos;ve rebuilt the entire platform from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- more --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-new&quot;&gt;What&apos;s New&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;redesigned-interface&quot;&gt;Redesigned Interface&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new UI is cleaner, faster, and more intuitive. We&apos;ve reduced click paths by 40% for common actions and introduced a unified command palette for power users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;real-time-collaboration&quot;&gt;Real-time Collaboration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple team members can now edit the same board simultaneously. You&apos;ll see cursors, selections, and changes in real-time — just like Google Docs, but for project management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;performance&quot;&gt;Performance&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire frontend has been rebuilt with modern tooling:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;60% faster&lt;/strong&gt; initial page load&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3x faster&lt;/strong&gt; search across large workspaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offline mode&lt;/strong&gt; with automatic sync when back online&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;migration&quot;&gt;Migration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Existing users will be automatically migrated to v2.0 over the next two weeks. No action is required — all your data, integrations, and settings will be preserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-next&quot;&gt;What&apos;s Next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re already working on v2.1, which will include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI-powered task suggestions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced automation workflows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Native mobile app refresh&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone who participated in our beta program. Your feedback shaped every pixel of this release.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>5 Strategies for Remote Team Productivity</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:3000/blog/remote-teams-productivity/" />
    <id>http://localhost:3000/blog/remote-teams-productivity/</id>
    <updated>2026-01-27T15:00:00Z</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Managing a remote team is more than just moving meetings to video calls. After working with thousands of distributed teams, we&apos;ve identified the strategies that actually move the needle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- more --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-async-first-communication&quot;&gt;1. Async-First Communication&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not every conversation needs to happen in real-time. Encourage your team to default to written updates, recorded demos, and threaded discussions. Reserve synchronous time for brainstorming and relationship building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-clear-ownership&quot;&gt;2. Clear Ownership&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every task, project, and decision should have a single owner. This doesn&apos;t mean working alone — it means someone is responsible for driving progress and communicating status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-visible-work&quot;&gt;3. Visible Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you can&apos;t see your colleagues at their desks, work needs to be visible in other ways. Use shared boards, daily standups (async or sync), and progress dashboards to keep everyone informed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-time-zone-awareness&quot;&gt;4. Time Zone Awareness&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overlapping hours are precious. Use them for collaborative work and meetings. Use non-overlapping hours for deep focus work. Document decisions so no one wakes up confused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-intentional-culture&quot;&gt;5. Intentional Culture&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remote culture doesn&apos;t happen by accident. Schedule virtual social events, celebrate wins publicly, and create spaces for non-work conversations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FlowSync&apos;s async features — comment threads, recorded updates, and timezone-aware scheduling — are designed to support these strategies out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>New Integrations: GitHub, Linear, and Notion</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:3000/blog/integrations-update/" />
    <id>http://localhost:3000/blog/integrations-update/</id>
    <updated>2026-01-09T15:00:00Z</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ve just shipped three of our most-requested integrations. FlowSync now connects seamlessly with &lt;strong&gt;GitHub&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Linear&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Notion&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- more --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;github&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sync pull requests, issues, and deployments directly to your FlowSync boards. When a PR is merged, the linked task automatically moves to &amp;quot;Done.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key features:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two-way sync for issues and PRs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deployment status tracking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Branch name auto-linking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;linear&quot;&gt;Linear&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Already using Linear for issue tracking? No problem. FlowSync&apos;s Linear integration lets you view and manage Linear issues alongside your FlowSync tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key features:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Import Linear projects as FlowSync boards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bi-directional status sync&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Label and priority mapping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;notion&quot;&gt;Notion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Embed Notion pages directly in FlowSync tasks, or create Notion docs from task descriptions with one click.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key features:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notion page embeds in task details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One-click doc creation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search across both platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;setting-up&quot;&gt;Setting Up&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All three integrations are available now for Pro and Enterprise plans. Head to &lt;strong&gt;Settings &amp;gt; Integrations&lt;/strong&gt; in your workspace to connect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re adding new integrations every month. &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hello@flowsync.app&quot;&gt;Let us know&lt;/a&gt; which tools you&apos;d like to see next.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
